2022-04-19T19:05:29.857435413Z  * Serving Flask app 'app' (lazy loading)
2022-04-19T19:05:29.857492005Z  * Environment: production
2022-04-19T19:05:29.857494595Z    WARNING: This is a development server. Do not use it in a production deployment.
2022-04-19T19:05:29.857502035Z    Use a production WSGI server instead.
2022-04-19T19:05:29.857504025Z  * Debug mode: off
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416498100Z sentence 0
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416527491Z 	word 0: My 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416530781Z 	word 1: name 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416532781Z 	word 2: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416534621Z 	word 3: Robin 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416536491Z 	word 4: Hood 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416538351Z sentence 0
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416540081Z 	word 0: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416541941Z 	word 1: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416543771Z 	word 2: day 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416545521Z 	word 3: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416547301Z 	word 4: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416549071Z 	word 5: referendum 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416550911Z 	word 6: michael 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416552721Z 	word 7: ashcroft 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416554531Z 	word 8: polling 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416556321Z 	word 9: team 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416558121Z 	word 10: questioned 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416559952Z 	word 11: 12,369 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416561721Z 	word 12: people 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416563561Z 	word 13: who 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416577922Z 	word 14: had 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416579862Z 	word 15: completed 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416581682Z 	word 16: voting 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416583512Z 	word 17: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416585302Z sentence 1
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416587012Z 	word 0: rpms 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416588802Z 	word 1: are 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416590612Z 	word 2: often 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416592452Z 	word 3: collected 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416594282Z 	word 4: centrally 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416596092Z 	word 5: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416597882Z 	word 6: one 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416599672Z 	word 7: or 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416601452Z 	word 8: more 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416603262Z 	word 9: software 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416605062Z 	word 10: repository 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416606872Z 	word 11: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416608672Z 	word 12: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416610473Z 	word 13: internet 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416612242Z 	word 14: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416614033Z sentence 2
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416615733Z 	word 0: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416617533Z 	word 1: 1991 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416619303Z 	word 2: he 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416621103Z 	word 3: played 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416622903Z 	word 4: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416624753Z 	word 5: two 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416626553Z 	word 6: teams 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416628353Z 	word 7: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416630153Z 	word 8: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416632013Z 	word 9: orlando 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416633833Z 	word 10: predators 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416635653Z 	word 11: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416637433Z 	word 12: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416639233Z 	word 13: dallas 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416643553Z 	word 14: texans 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416645443Z 	word 15: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416647213Z sentence 3
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416648913Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416650693Z 	word 1: original 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416652463Z 	word 2: game 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416654233Z 	word 3: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416656033Z 	word 4: released 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416658333Z 	word 5: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416660183Z 	word 6: ms-dos 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416662014Z 	word 7: first 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416663803Z 	word 8: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416665564Z 	word 9: then 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416667364Z 	word 10: commodore 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416669184Z 	word 11: amiga 	|	 prediction: I-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416670984Z 	word 12: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416672754Z 	word 13: amiga 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416674544Z 	word 14: cd32 	|	 prediction: I-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416676344Z 	word 15: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416678124Z 	word 16: apple 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416681054Z 	word 17: macintosh 	|	 prediction: I-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416683364Z 	word 18: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416685134Z 	word 19: sega 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416686934Z 	word 20: saturn 	|	 prediction: I-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416688724Z 	word 21: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416690504Z 	word 22: playstation 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416692334Z 	word 23: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416694114Z sentence 4
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416695814Z 	word 0: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416697584Z 	word 1: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416699364Z 	word 2: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416701144Z 	word 3: seventh 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416702944Z 	word 4: edition 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416704724Z 	word 5: conducted 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416706514Z 	word 6: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416710524Z 	word 7: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416712355Z 	word 8: united 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416714175Z 	word 9: states 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416715955Z 	word 10: golf 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416717745Z 	word 11: association 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416719555Z 	word 12: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416721335Z 	word 13: usga 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416723115Z 	word 14: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416724905Z 	word 15: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416726675Z sentence 5
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416728365Z 	word 0: tom 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416730155Z 	word 1: fogerty 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416731955Z 	word 2: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416734305Z 	word 3: rhythm 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416736195Z 	word 4: guitar 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416738005Z 	word 5: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416739815Z 	word 6: backing 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416741625Z 	word 7: vocals 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416743395Z 	word 8: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416745175Z 	word 9: 1967 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416747005Z 	word 10: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416748795Z 	word 11: 1971 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416750605Z 	word 12: ; 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416752465Z 	word 13: died 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416756125Z 	word 14: 1990 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416757945Z 	word 15: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416759745Z sentence 6
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416761456Z 	word 0: isabel 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416763285Z 	word 1: mclaughlin 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416765126Z 	word 2: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416766976Z 	word 3: 1903 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416768776Z 	word 4: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416770546Z 	word 5: 2002 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416772326Z 	word 6: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416774096Z 	word 7: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416776086Z 	word 8: artist 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416780026Z 	word 9: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416781866Z 	word 10: patron 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416783656Z 	word 11: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416785496Z 	word 12: philanthropist 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416787326Z 	word 13: ; 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416789136Z 	word 14: member 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416790916Z 	word 15: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416792716Z 	word 16: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416794496Z 	word 17: canadian 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416796326Z 	word 18: group 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416798156Z 	word 19: of 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416799996Z 	word 20: painters 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416801876Z sentence 7
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416803676Z 	word 0: he 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416805476Z 	word 1: has 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416807286Z 	word 2: fought 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416809066Z 	word 3: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416810837Z 	word 4: many 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416812606Z 	word 5: well 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416814377Z 	word 6: known 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416816187Z 	word 7: mixed 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416817957Z 	word 8: martial 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416819747Z 	word 9: arts 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416821517Z 	word 10: organizations 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416823327Z 	word 11: as 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416825117Z 	word 12: shooto 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416826897Z 	word 13: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416828667Z 	word 14: deep 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416830447Z 	word 15: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416832217Z 	word 16: bellator 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416834047Z 	word 17: mma 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416835867Z 	word 18: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416837637Z sentence 8
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416839317Z 	word 0: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416841097Z 	word 1: pickup 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416845347Z 	word 2: truck 	|	 prediction: I-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416847197Z 	word 3: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416848957Z 	word 4: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416850727Z 	word 5: sometimes 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416852537Z 	word 6: called 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416854307Z 	word 7: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416856077Z 	word 8: dually 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416857838Z 	word 9: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416859607Z sentence 9
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416861298Z 	word 0: she 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416863078Z 	word 1: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416864858Z 	word 2: research 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416866678Z 	word 3: fellow 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416868448Z 	word 4: at 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416870228Z 	word 5: somerville 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416872058Z 	word 6: college 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416873848Z 	word 7: from 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416875608Z 	word 8: 1957 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416877388Z 	word 9: until 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416879168Z 	word 10: 1960 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416880938Z 	word 11: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416882708Z sentence 10
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416884418Z 	word 0: christina 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416886188Z 	word 1: aguilera 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416888008Z 	word 2: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416889778Z 	word 3: pink 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416891568Z 	word 4: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416894228Z 	word 5: lil' 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416896048Z 	word 6: kim 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416897828Z 	word 7: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416899608Z 	word 8: mýa 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416901458Z 	word 9: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416903268Z 	word 10: lady 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416905068Z 	word 11: marmalade 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416906878Z sentence 11
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416910588Z 	word 0: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416912379Z 	word 1: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416914169Z 	word 2: listed 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416915949Z 	word 3: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416917709Z 	word 4: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416919479Z 	word 5: national 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416921289Z 	word 6: register 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416923089Z 	word 7: of 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416924889Z 	word 8: historic 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416926669Z 	word 9: places 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416928459Z 	word 10: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416930219Z 	word 11: 1982 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416932009Z 	word 12: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416933789Z sentence 12
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416935489Z 	word 0: often 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416937259Z 	word 1: contracted 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416939059Z 	word 2: as 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416940819Z 	word 3: tu 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416942599Z 	word 4: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416944379Z 	word 5: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416946149Z 	word 6: organization 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416947949Z 	word 7: began 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416949719Z 	word 8: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416951489Z 	word 9: 1959 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416953289Z 	word 10: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416955059Z 	word 11: michigan 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416956829Z 	word 12: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416958589Z sentence 13
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416960280Z 	word 0: she 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416962100Z 	word 1: studied 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416963930Z 	word 2: chemistry 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416965740Z 	word 3: at 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416967520Z 	word 4: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416969280Z 	word 5: vietnam 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416971090Z 	word 6: national 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416974950Z 	word 7: university 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416976780Z 	word 8: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416978560Z 	word 9: which 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416980330Z 	word 10: she 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416982110Z 	word 11: graduated 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416983890Z 	word 12: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416985650Z 	word 13: 1992 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416987410Z 	word 14: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416989160Z sentence 14
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416990850Z 	word 0: coldspring 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416992620Z 	word 1: shares 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416994380Z 	word 2: its 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416996150Z 	word 3: western 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416997920Z 	word 4: border 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.416999690Z 	word 5: with 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417001460Z 	word 6: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417003240Z 	word 7: towns 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417004990Z 	word 8: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417006761Z 	word 9: south 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417008561Z 	word 10: valley 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417010721Z 	word 11: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417012510Z 	word 12: randolph 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417014301Z 	word 13: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417016081Z sentence 15
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417017751Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417019501Z 	word 1: film 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417021271Z 	word 2: garnered 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417023061Z 	word 3: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417024821Z 	word 4: 33 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417026571Z 	word 5: % 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417028341Z 	word 6: approval 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417030131Z 	word 7: rating 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417031901Z 	word 8: from 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417033671Z 	word 9: 6 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417035441Z 	word 10: critics 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417037221Z 	word 11: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417041051Z 	word 12: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417042871Z 	word 13: mixed 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417059102Z 	word 14: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417061031Z 	word 15: negative 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417062812Z 	word 16: rating 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417064572Z 	word 17: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417066322Z 	word 18: 4.1 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417068092Z 	word 19: out 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417069852Z 	word 20: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417071612Z 	word 21: 10 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417073362Z 	word 22: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417075202Z 	word 23: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417076972Z 	word 24: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417078742Z 	word 25: review 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417080582Z 	word 26: aggregate 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417082352Z 	word 27: website 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417084212Z 	word 28: rotten 	|	 prediction: B-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417086022Z 	word 29: tomatoes 	|	 prediction: I-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417087812Z 	word 30: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417089572Z sentence 16
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417091252Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417093012Z 	word 1: 2018 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417094792Z 	word 2: expansion 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417096562Z 	word 3: team 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417098342Z 	word 4: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417100102Z 	word 5: los 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417101892Z 	word 6: angeles 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417103682Z 	word 7: fc 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417105462Z 	word 8: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417107212Z 	word 9: had 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417108972Z 	word 10: selection 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417110743Z 	word 11: 23 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417112493Z 	word 12: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417114263Z sentence 17
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417115933Z 	word 0: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417120673Z 	word 1: 1882 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417122493Z 	word 2: he 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417124263Z 	word 3: planted 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417126033Z 	word 4: rubber 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417127823Z 	word 5: seeds 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417129583Z 	word 6: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417131343Z 	word 7: grew 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417133113Z 	word 8: seven 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417134893Z 	word 9: trees 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417136663Z 	word 10: at 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417138423Z 	word 11: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417140203Z 	word 12: gardens 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417141973Z 	word 13: at 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417144173Z 	word 14: kuala 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417145993Z 	word 15: kangsar 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417147783Z 	word 16: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417149543Z sentence 18
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417151223Z 	word 0: some 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417153003Z 	word 1: populations 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417154803Z 	word 2: are 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417156573Z 	word 3: still 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417158344Z 	word 4: considerably 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417160153Z 	word 5: worse 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417161904Z 	word 6: off 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417163674Z 	word 7: today 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417165424Z 	word 8: than 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417167194Z 	word 9: they 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417168964Z 	word 10: were 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417170724Z 	word 11: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417172484Z 	word 12: 1989 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417174264Z 	word 13: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417176014Z 	word 14: e.g. 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417177794Z 	word 15: moldova 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417179574Z 	word 16: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417181334Z 	word 17: serbia 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417185234Z 	word 18: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417187044Z 	word 19: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417188804Z sentence 19
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417190484Z 	word 0: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417192264Z 	word 1: flows 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417194014Z 	word 2: into 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417195794Z 	word 3: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417197554Z 	word 4: usa 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417199334Z 	word 5: near 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417201114Z 	word 6: friedberg 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417202904Z 	word 7: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417205945Z sentence 20
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417207654Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417209425Z 	word 1: refreshing 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417211265Z 	word 2: sight 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417213045Z 	word 3: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417214815Z 	word 4: sound 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417216575Z 	word 5: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417218335Z 	word 6: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417220105Z 	word 7: splashing 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417221895Z 	word 8: fountains 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417223675Z 	word 9: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417225435Z 	word 10: cascades 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417227215Z 	word 11: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417228985Z 	word 12: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417230765Z 	word 13: luxuriant 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417232555Z 	word 14: gardens 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417234355Z 	word 15: must 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417236125Z 	word 16: have 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417237895Z 	word 17: provided 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417239675Z 	word 18: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417241435Z 	word 19: welcome 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417243215Z 	word 20: relief 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417244995Z 	word 21: from 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417246765Z 	word 22: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417253335Z 	word 23: heat 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417255146Z 	word 24: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417256906Z 	word 25: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417258695Z 	word 26: tunisia 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417260475Z 	word 27: summer 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417262266Z 	word 28: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417264056Z sentence 21
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417266046Z 	word 0: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417267866Z 	word 1: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417269696Z 	word 2: acquired 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417271486Z 	word 3: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417273246Z 	word 4: hewlett-packard 	|	 prediction: B-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417275066Z 	word 5: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417276836Z 	word 6: 2007 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417278606Z 	word 7: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417280366Z sentence 22
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417282066Z 	word 0: achema 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417283826Z 	word 1: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417285586Z 	word 2: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417287356Z 	word 3: largest 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417289136Z 	word 4: fertilizer 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417290916Z 	word 5: factory 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417292696Z 	word 6: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417294456Z 	word 7: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417296226Z 	word 8: baltic 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417298026Z 	word 9: states 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417299816Z 	word 10: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417301576Z 	word 11: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417303356Z 	word 12: located 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417305156Z 	word 13: nearby 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417306927Z 	word 14: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417308696Z sentence 23
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417310396Z 	word 0: ruehl 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417312167Z 	word 1: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417313937Z 	word 2: known 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417317807Z 	word 3: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417319647Z 	word 4: her 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417321417Z 	word 5: leading 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417323217Z 	word 6: performance 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417325037Z 	word 7: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417326807Z 	word 8: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417328567Z 	word 9: play 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417330347Z 	word 10: lost 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417332157Z 	word 11: in 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417333967Z 	word 12: yonkers 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417335757Z 	word 13: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417337537Z 	word 14: supporting 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417339337Z 	word 15: performance 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417341117Z 	word 16: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417342887Z 	word 17: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417344687Z 	word 18: film 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417346457Z 	word 19: the 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417348247Z 	word 20: fisher 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417350047Z 	word 21: king 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417351837Z 	word 22: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417353617Z sentence 24
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417355297Z 	word 0: çeştepe 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417357168Z 	word 1: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417358948Z 	word 2: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417360728Z 	word 3: town 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417362488Z 	word 4: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417364258Z 	word 5: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417366028Z 	word 6: central 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417367808Z 	word 7: district 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417369568Z 	word 8: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417371338Z 	word 9: aydın 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417373188Z 	word 10: province 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417375008Z 	word 11: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417376778Z 	word 12: turkey 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417378568Z 	word 13: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417383598Z sentence 25
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417385378Z 	word 0: an 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417387158Z 	word 1: image 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417388938Z 	word 2: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417390718Z 	word 3: called 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417392498Z 	word 4: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417394258Z 	word 5: true 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417396058Z 	word 6: color 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417397848Z 	word 7: image 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417399628Z 	word 8: when 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417401408Z 	word 9: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417403178Z 	word 10: offers 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417404958Z 	word 11: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417406729Z 	word 12: natural 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417408529Z 	word 13: color 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417410309Z 	word 14: rendition 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417412089Z 	word 15: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417413859Z 	word 16: or 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417415639Z 	word 17: when 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417417419Z 	word 18: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417419199Z 	word 19: comes 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417420979Z 	word 20: close 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417422769Z 	word 21: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417424539Z 	word 22: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417426299Z 	word 23: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417428069Z sentence 26
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417429769Z 	word 0: however 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417431549Z 	word 1: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417433329Z 	word 2: large 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417435109Z 	word 3: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417436889Z 	word 4: heavy 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417438659Z 	word 5: components 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417440449Z 	word 6: like 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417442899Z 	word 7: generator 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417444769Z 	word 8: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417446549Z 	word 9: gearbox 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417450349Z 	word 10: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417452159Z 	word 11: blades 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417453930Z 	word 12: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417455690Z 	word 13: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417457570Z 	word 14: so 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417459339Z 	word 15: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417461160Z 	word 16: are 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417462950Z 	word 17: rarely 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417464720Z 	word 18: replaced 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417466500Z 	word 19: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417468280Z 	word 20: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417470070Z 	word 21: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417471840Z 	word 22: mobile 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417473640Z 	word 23: crane 	|	 prediction: I-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417475420Z 	word 24: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417477180Z 	word 25: needed 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417478960Z 	word 26: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417480730Z 	word 27: those 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417482500Z 	word 28: cases 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417484280Z 	word 29: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417486050Z sentence 27
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417487730Z 	word 0: science 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417489500Z 	word 1: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417491270Z 	word 2: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417493040Z 	word 3: human 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417494820Z 	word 4: temperament 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417496810Z 	word 5: allen 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:40.417498600Z 	word 6: & 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.207974280Z 	word 7: unwin 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208005180Z 	word 8: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208007531Z 	word 9: translated 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208009511Z 	word 10: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208011401Z 	word 11: introduced 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208013211Z 	word 12: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208031481Z 	word 13: james 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208033571Z 	word 14: vincent 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208035401Z 	word 15: murphy 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208037311Z 	word 16: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208039091Z 	word 17: with 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208040881Z 	word 18: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208042651Z 	word 19: foreword 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208044481Z 	word 20: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208046241Z 	word 21: ernest 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208048021Z 	word 22: rutherford 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208049821Z sentence 28
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208051541Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208053311Z 	word 1: oldest 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208055072Z 	word 2: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208056841Z 	word 3: three 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208058601Z 	word 4: siblings 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208060382Z 	word 5: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208062142Z 	word 6: she 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208063892Z 	word 7: grew 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208065662Z 	word 8: up 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208067402Z 	word 9: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208069132Z 	word 10: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208070902Z 	word 11: nearby 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208072662Z 	word 12: delta 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208074432Z 	word 13: town 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208076212Z 	word 14: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208077952Z 	word 15: hinthada 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208079722Z 	word 16: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208081472Z 	word 17: hinthada 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208083222Z 	word 18: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208084952Z 	word 19: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208086702Z 	word 20: before 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208088472Z 	word 21: moving 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208090212Z 	word 22: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208094322Z 	word 23: yangon 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208096172Z 	word 24: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208097932Z 	word 25: yangon 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208099722Z 	word 26: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208101492Z 	word 27: as 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208103242Z 	word 28: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208105033Z 	word 29: teenager 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208106782Z 	word 30: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208108522Z sentence 29
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208110173Z 	word 0: he 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208111943Z 	word 1: showed 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208113703Z 	word 2: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208115463Z 	word 3: script 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208117203Z 	word 4: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208118983Z 	word 5: his 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208120753Z 	word 6: literary 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208122513Z 	word 7: agent 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208124273Z 	word 8: who 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208126003Z 	word 9: gave 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208127753Z 	word 10: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208129483Z 	word 11: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208131233Z 	word 12: mike 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208133603Z 	word 13: medavoy 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208135453Z 	word 14: who 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208137223Z 	word 15: attached 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208138983Z 	word 16: director 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208140813Z 	word 17: karel 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208142613Z 	word 18: reisz 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208144403Z 	word 19: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208146143Z sentence 30
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208147823Z 	word 0: we 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208149573Z 	word 1: only 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208151323Z 	word 2: want 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208153083Z 	word 3: four 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208154834Z 	word 4: or 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208156574Z 	word 5: five 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208160634Z 	word 6: sarong 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208162434Z 	word 7: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208164174Z 	word 8: we 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208165914Z 	word 9: do 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208167654Z 	word 10: nt 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208169404Z 	word 11: need 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208171154Z 	word 12: trousers 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208172964Z 	word 13: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208174704Z sentence 31
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208176364Z 	word 0: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208178104Z 	word 1: 2006 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208179914Z 	word 2: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208181654Z 	word 3: aged 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208183394Z 	word 4: 16 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208185134Z 	word 5: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208186874Z 	word 6: štěch 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208189504Z 	word 7: signed 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208191314Z 	word 8: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208193114Z 	word 9: premier 	|	 prediction: B-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208194964Z 	word 10: league 	|	 prediction: I-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208196754Z 	word 11: club 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208198564Z 	word 12: west 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208200364Z 	word 13: ham 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208202154Z 	word 14: united 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208203944Z 	word 15: f.c. 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208205704Z 	word 16: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208207504Z 	word 17: an 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208209295Z 	word 18: undisclosed 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208211125Z 	word 19: fee 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208212895Z 	word 20: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208214675Z sentence 0
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208216375Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208218145Z 	word 1: g 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208219915Z 	word 2: day 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208221675Z 	word 3: : 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208225625Z 	word 4: viktor 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208227475Z 	word 5: orbán 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208229275Z 	word 6: cuts 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208231035Z 	word 7: ties 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208232775Z 	word 8: with 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208234525Z 	word 9: lajos 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208236275Z 	word 10: simicska 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208238075Z 	word 11: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208239845Z 	word 12: former 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208241635Z 	word 13: economic 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208243425Z 	word 14: ally 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208245185Z 	word 15: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208246955Z sentence 1
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208248615Z 	word 0: phaedra 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208250575Z 	word 1: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208252376Z 	word 2: monodrama 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208254196Z 	word 3: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208255965Z 	word 4: mezzo 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208257736Z 	word 5: soprano 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208259576Z 	word 6: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208263596Z 	word 7: orchestra 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208265446Z 	word 8: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208267386Z 	word 9: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208269246Z 	word 10: george 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208271026Z 	word 11: rochberg 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208272786Z 	word 12: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208274616Z 	word 13: 1973 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208276376Z 	word 14: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208278186Z 	word 15: 1974 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208279966Z sentence 2
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208281636Z 	word 0: floppy 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208283436Z 	word 1: disk 	|	 prediction: I-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208285206Z 	word 2: drives 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208286976Z 	word 3: are 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208288716Z 	word 4: rarely 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208292566Z 	word 5: fitted 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208294366Z 	word 6: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208296116Z 	word 7: modern 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208297876Z 	word 8: computers 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208299626Z 	word 9: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208301366Z 	word 10: are 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208303117Z 	word 11: obsolete 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208304866Z 	word 12: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208306697Z 	word 13: normal 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208308517Z 	word 14: purposes 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208310277Z 	word 15: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208312047Z 	word 16: although 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208313797Z 	word 17: internal 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208315547Z 	word 18: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208317287Z 	word 19: external 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208319047Z 	word 20: drives 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208334387Z 	word 21: can 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208339007Z 	word 22: be 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208340807Z 	word 23: fitted 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208342557Z 	word 24: if 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208344297Z 	word 25: required 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208346037Z 	word 26: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208347787Z sentence 3
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208349437Z 	word 0: while 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208351187Z 	word 1: they 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208352927Z 	word 2: raised 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208354718Z 	word 3: three 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208356447Z 	word 4: children 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208359148Z 	word 5: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208360908Z 	word 6: she 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208362638Z 	word 7: taught 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208364388Z 	word 8: part 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208366128Z 	word 9: time 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208367868Z 	word 10: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208369608Z 	word 11: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208374658Z 	word 12: workers' 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208376518Z 	word 13: educational 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208378298Z 	word 14: association 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208380068Z 	word 15: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208381798Z 	word 16: began 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208383558Z 	word 17: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208385958Z 	word 18: writing 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208387768Z 	word 19: career 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208389518Z 	word 20: that 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208391268Z 	word 21: lasted 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208393038Z 	word 22: into 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208394788Z 	word 23: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208396528Z 	word 24: 1980s 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208398288Z 	word 25: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208400038Z sentence 4
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208401699Z 	word 0: present 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208403459Z 	word 1: south 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208405208Z 	word 2: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208406948Z 	word 3: west 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208408699Z 	word 4: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208410459Z 	word 5: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208412199Z 	word 6: line 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208413959Z 	word 7: drawn 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208415699Z 	word 8: from 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208417449Z 	word 9: syracuse 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208419229Z 	word 10: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208420979Z 	word 11: cefalù 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208422809Z 	word 12: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208424569Z sentence 5
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208426229Z 	word 0: versions 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208427989Z 	word 1: have 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208429729Z 	word 2: been 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208431469Z 	word 3: created 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208433219Z 	word 4: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208434959Z 	word 5: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208439059Z 	word 6: playstation 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208440899Z 	word 7: portable 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208442659Z 	word 8: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208444399Z 	word 9: game 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208446159Z 	word 10: boy 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208447939Z 	word 11: advance 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208449689Z 	word 12: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208451480Z 	word 13: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208453249Z 	word 14: nintendo 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208455020Z 	word 15: ds 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208456789Z 	word 16: platforms 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208458610Z 	word 17: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208460360Z sentence 6
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208462020Z 	word 0: eicher 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208463780Z 	word 1: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208465520Z 	word 2: john 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208467290Z 	word 3: h 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208469050Z 	word 4: . 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208470780Z 	word 5: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208472550Z 	word 6: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208474280Z 	word 7: david 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208476040Z 	word 8: j. 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208477800Z 	word 9: eicher 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208479630Z 	word 10: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208481390Z 	word 11: civil 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208483140Z 	word 12: war 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208484890Z 	word 13: high 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208486710Z 	word 14: commands 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208488470Z 	word 15: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208490210Z sentence 7
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208491860Z 	word 0: they 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208493610Z 	word 1: were 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208495370Z 	word 2: first 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208497110Z 	word 3: synthesized 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208498910Z 	word 4: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208503670Z 	word 5: alexander 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208505561Z 	word 6: shulgin 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208507341Z 	word 7: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208509091Z 	word 8: written 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208510851Z 	word 9: up 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208512601Z 	word 10: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208514341Z 	word 11: his 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208516101Z 	word 12: book 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208517861Z 	word 13: pihkal 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208519641Z 	word 14: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208521391Z sentence 8
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208523071Z 	word 0: other 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208524811Z 	word 1: stations 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208526571Z 	word 2: within 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208528361Z 	word 3: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208530091Z 	word 4: limits 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208531851Z 	word 5: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208533591Z 	word 6: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208535351Z 	word 7: municipality 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208537121Z 	word 8: are 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208538871Z 	word 9: 's-hertogenbosch 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208540681Z 	word 10: oost 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208542441Z 	word 11: railway 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208544211Z 	word 12: station 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208545991Z 	word 13: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208547731Z 	word 14: rosmalen 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208549491Z 	word 15: railway 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208551251Z 	word 16: station 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208553011Z 	word 17: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208554762Z sentence 9
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208556422Z 	word 0: because 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208558182Z 	word 1: they 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208559932Z 	word 2: go 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208561682Z 	word 3: canvassing 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208563452Z 	word 4: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208567212Z 	word 5: they 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208569002Z 	word 6: are 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208570742Z 	word 7: able 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208572492Z 	word 8: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208574232Z 	word 9: reach 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208575982Z 	word 10: beyond 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208577742Z 	word 11: established 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208579512Z 	word 12: organizations 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208581282Z 	word 13: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208583022Z 	word 14: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208584762Z 	word 15: churched 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208586532Z 	word 16: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208588282Z 	word 17: bring 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208590032Z 	word 18: together 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208591802Z 	word 19: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208593562Z 	word 20: wide 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208595302Z 	word 21: range 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208597062Z 	word 22: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208598812Z 	word 23: less 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208600552Z 	word 24: privileged 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208602312Z 	word 25: people 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208604072Z 	word 26: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208605843Z sentence 10
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208607533Z 	word 0: salamucha 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208609293Z 	word 1: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208611033Z 	word 2: sent 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208612963Z 	word 3: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208614723Z 	word 4: sachsenhausen 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208616533Z 	word 5: concentration 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208618303Z 	word 6: camp 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208620073Z 	word 7: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208621813Z 	word 8: 1940 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208623553Z 	word 9: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208625303Z sentence 11
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208626983Z 	word 0: charlie 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208630933Z 	word 1: brooker 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208632743Z 	word 2: stated 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208634493Z 	word 3: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208636233Z 	word 4: an 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208637983Z 	word 5: interview 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208653764Z 	word 6: that 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208656554Z 	word 7: this 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208658324Z 	word 8: episode 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208660074Z 	word 9: influenced 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208661844Z 	word 10: fifteen 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208663614Z 	word 11: million 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208665384Z 	word 12: merits 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208667154Z 	word 13: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208668904Z 	word 14: an 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208670654Z 	word 15: episode 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208672424Z 	word 16: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208674174Z 	word 17: his 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208675924Z 	word 18: anthology 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208677684Z 	word 19: series 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208680424Z 	word 20: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208682184Z 	word 21: black 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208683954Z 	word 22: mirror 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208685814Z 	word 23: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208687574Z sentence 12
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208689234Z 	word 0: ldi 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208690994Z 	word 1: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208692734Z 	word 2: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208694494Z 	word 3: full 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208696244Z 	word 4: service 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208698004Z 	word 5: pharmacy 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208699765Z 	word 6: benefit 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208701525Z 	word 7: manager 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208703274Z 	word 8: based 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208705025Z 	word 9: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208706765Z 	word 10: st. 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208711785Z 	word 11: louis 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208713615Z 	word 12: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208715355Z sentence 13
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208717025Z 	word 0: she 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208718765Z 	word 1: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208720505Z 	word 2: notorious 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208722265Z 	word 3: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208724015Z 	word 4: fashioning 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208725765Z 	word 5: her 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208727515Z 	word 6: beard 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208729265Z 	word 7: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208731005Z 	word 8: imitate 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208732755Z 	word 9: that 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208734485Z 	word 10: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208736235Z 	word 11: napoleon 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208738015Z 	word 12: iii 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208739775Z 	word 13: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208741495Z sentence 14
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208743145Z 	word 0: she 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208745225Z 	word 1: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208747045Z 	word 2: one 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208748786Z 	word 3: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208750515Z 	word 4: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208752255Z 	word 5: most 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208754015Z 	word 6: popular 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208755766Z 	word 7: singers 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208757516Z 	word 8: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208759256Z 	word 9: poland 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208761016Z 	word 10: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208762756Z 	word 11: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208764526Z 	word 12: 1950s 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208766276Z 	word 13: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208768006Z sentence 15
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208769676Z 	word 0: us 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208771436Z 	word 1: and 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208773206Z 	word 2: them 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208777476Z 	word 3: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208779256Z 	word 4: godflesh 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208781026Z 	word 5: cover 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208782766Z 	word 6: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208784496Z 	word 7: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208786326Z 	word 8: 5 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208788076Z 	word 9: : 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208789846Z 	word 10: 35 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208791576Z sentence 16
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208793236Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208794976Z 	word 1: series 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208796726Z 	word 2: attracted 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208798487Z 	word 3: guests 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208800236Z 	word 4: such 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208801996Z 	word 5: as 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208803727Z 	word 6: bill 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208805497Z 	word 7: cosby 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208807257Z 	word 8: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208808997Z 	word 9: debbie 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208810757Z 	word 10: harry 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208812527Z 	word 11: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208814267Z 	word 12: billy 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208816037Z 	word 13: dee 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208817797Z 	word 14: williams 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208819557Z 	word 15: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208821297Z 	word 16: cheap 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208823037Z 	word 17: trick 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208824777Z 	word 18: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208826507Z 	word 19: patti 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208828257Z 	word 20: smith 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208830027Z 	word 21: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208831777Z 	word 22: brooke 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208833527Z 	word 23: shields 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208836147Z 	word 24: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208840757Z sentence 17
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208842477Z 	word 0: 2018 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208844227Z 	word 1: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208845997Z 	word 2: al-hilal 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208847767Z 	word 3: fc 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208849528Z 	word 4: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208851268Z 	word 5: appeal 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208853008Z 	word 6: won 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208854758Z 	word 7: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208856498Z 	word 8: al 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208858258Z 	word 9: merreikh 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208860018Z 	word 10: fc 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208861798Z 	word 11: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208866988Z 	word 12: but 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208868868Z 	word 13: later 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208870618Z 	word 14: overturned 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208872388Z 	word 15: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208874128Z 	word 16: south 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208875898Z 	word 17: sudan 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208877658Z 	word 18: football 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208879418Z 	word 19: association 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208881178Z 	word 20: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208882928Z sentence 18
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208884578Z 	word 0: their 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208886338Z 	word 1: music 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208888088Z 	word 2: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208889828Z 	word 3: compared 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208891588Z 	word 4: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208893328Z 	word 5: dead 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208895088Z 	word 6: can 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208896858Z 	word 7: dance 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208898629Z 	word 8: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208900369Z 	word 9: modest 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208902149Z 	word 10: petrovich 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208903919Z 	word 11: mussorgsky 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208908339Z 	word 12: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208910139Z 	word 13: especially 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208911939Z 	word 14: his 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208913699Z 	word 15: composition 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208915469Z 	word 16: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208917229Z 	word 17: nursery 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208918989Z 	word 18: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208920739Z sentence 19
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208922399Z 	word 0: don't 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208924169Z 	word 1: speak 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208925929Z 	word 2: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208927669Z 	word 3: no 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208929439Z 	word 4: doubt 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208931209Z 	word 5: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208932979Z 	word 6: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208934719Z 	word 7: top 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208936469Z 	word 8: 8 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208938209Z 	word 9: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208939949Z sentence 20
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208941609Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208943349Z 	word 1: school 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208945099Z 	word 2: 's 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208946839Z 	word 3: corridor 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208948590Z 	word 4: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208950350Z 	word 5: modeled 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208952130Z 	word 6: after 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208953880Z 	word 7: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208955630Z 	word 8: corridor 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208957390Z 	word 9: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208959130Z 	word 10: an 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208960870Z 	word 11: abbey 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208962620Z 	word 12: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208964370Z 	word 13: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208966110Z 	word 14: region 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208967870Z 	word 15: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208969620Z sentence 21
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208974540Z 	word 0: north 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208976330Z 	word 1: started 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208978080Z 	word 2: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.208979820Z 	word 3: webcomic 	|	 prediction: B-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999477399Z 	word 4: dinosaur 	|	 prediction: I-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999513640Z 	word 5: comics 	|	 prediction: I-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999516040Z 	word 6: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999518130Z 	word 7: 2003 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999519950Z 	word 8: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999521750Z 	word 9: during 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999523560Z 	word 10: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999525700Z 	word 11: last 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999527660Z 	word 12: year 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999529510Z 	word 13: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999531270Z 	word 14: his 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999533030Z 	word 15: undergraduate 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999534850Z 	word 16: degree 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999536630Z 	word 17: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999538380Z sentence 22
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999540090Z 	word 0: he 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999541840Z 	word 1: also 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999543600Z 	word 2: modelled 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999545400Z 	word 3: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999547170Z 	word 4: complete 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999548921Z 	word 5: course 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999550850Z 	word 6: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999552610Z 	word 7: fortification 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999554631Z 	word 8: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999556421Z 	word 9: 92 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999558201Z 	word 10: models 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999559961Z 	word 11: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999561721Z 	word 12: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999563471Z 	word 13: which 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999565221Z 	word 14: he 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999577581Z 	word 15: offered 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999579611Z 	word 16: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999581371Z 	word 17: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999583141Z 	word 18: committee 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999584921Z 	word 19: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999586701Z 	word 20: public 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999588511Z 	word 21: safety 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999590291Z 	word 22: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999592051Z sentence 23
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999593811Z 	word 0: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999595591Z 	word 1: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999597421Z 	word 2: considered 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999599182Z 	word 3: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999600922Z 	word 4: most 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999602691Z 	word 5: notable 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999604462Z 	word 6: ancient 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999606232Z 	word 7: structure 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999608002Z 	word 8: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999609772Z 	word 9: tel 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999611542Z 	word 10: rumeida 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999613312Z 	word 11: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999615062Z sentence 24
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999616742Z 	word 0: pindjur 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999618492Z 	word 1: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999620252Z 	word 2: similar 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999622002Z 	word 3: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999623752Z 	word 4: ajvar 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999625502Z 	word 5: but 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999627272Z 	word 6: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999629012Z 	word 7: generally 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999630772Z 	word 8: made 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999632522Z 	word 9: with 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999634332Z 	word 10: eggplants 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999636562Z 	word 11: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999638362Z sentence 25
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999642292Z 	word 0: infant 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999644132Z 	word 1: formula 	|	 prediction: I-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999645922Z 	word 2: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999647672Z 	word 3: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999649423Z 	word 4: food 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999651172Z 	word 5: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999652932Z 	word 6: infants 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999654693Z sentence 26
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999656373Z 	word 0: mikael 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999658163Z 	word 1: pernfors 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999659933Z 	word 2: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999661683Z 	word 3: fourth 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999663463Z 	word 4: round 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999665203Z 	word 5: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999666953Z 	word 6: lost 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999668693Z 	word 7: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999670443Z 	word 8: boris 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999672223Z 	word 9: becker 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999674033Z 	word 10: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999675783Z sentence 27
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999677443Z 	word 0: she 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999679193Z 	word 1: also 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999681013Z 	word 2: worked 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999684253Z 	word 3: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999686033Z 	word 4: excavating 	|	 prediction: B-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999687793Z 	word 5: artifacts 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999689553Z 	word 6: related 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999691303Z 	word 7: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999693053Z 	word 8: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999694793Z 	word 9: gortyn 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999696593Z 	word 10: code 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999698333Z 	word 11: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999700073Z 	word 12: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999701833Z 	word 13: most 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999703594Z 	word 14: noted 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999705344Z 	word 15: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999710114Z 	word 16: her 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999711924Z 	word 17: publications 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999713704Z 	word 18: regarding 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999715494Z 	word 19: that 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999717264Z 	word 20: inscription 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999719054Z 	word 21: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999720834Z sentence 28
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999722504Z 	word 0: he 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999724314Z 	word 1: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999726074Z 	word 2: created 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999727834Z 	word 3: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999745044Z 	word 4: robert 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999749674Z 	word 5: bernstein 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999751494Z 	word 6: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999753265Z 	word 7: kurt 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999755045Z 	word 8: schaffenberger 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999756855Z 	word 9: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999758615Z sentence 29
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999760295Z 	word 0: he 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999762285Z 	word 1: has 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999764255Z 	word 2: adapted 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999766025Z 	word 3: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999767785Z 	word 4: number 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999769555Z 	word 5: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999771325Z 	word 6: poet 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999773105Z 	word 7: nick 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999775765Z 	word 8: flynn 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999777585Z 	word 9: pieces 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999779365Z 	word 10: into 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999781195Z 	word 11: comics 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999782975Z 	word 12: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999784735Z 	word 13: which 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999786505Z 	word 14: have 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999788275Z 	word 15: appeared 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999790065Z 	word 16: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999795515Z 	word 17: various 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999797335Z 	word 18: literary 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999799106Z 	word 19: journals 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999800886Z 	word 20: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999802635Z 	word 21: websites 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999804406Z 	word 22: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999806176Z sentence 30
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999807846Z 	word 0: exclaim! 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999809616Z 	word 1: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999811366Z 	word 2: reviewing 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999813126Z 	word 3: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999814876Z 	word 4: reissue 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999816696Z 	word 5: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999818446Z 	word 6: called 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999820206Z 	word 7: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999822046Z 	word 8: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999823796Z 	word 9: dopey 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999825556Z 	word 10: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999827306Z 	word 11: young 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999829066Z 	word 12: record 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999830826Z 	word 13: that 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999832586Z 	word 14: basically 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999834356Z 	word 15: defies 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999836116Z 	word 16: serious 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999837876Z 	word 17: criticism 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999839646Z 	word 18: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999841406Z sentence 31
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999843076Z 	word 0: dosco 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999844836Z 	word 1: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999846596Z 	word 2: purchased 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999848356Z 	word 3: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999850107Z 	word 4: 1957 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999851867Z 	word 5: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999853617Z 	word 6: avro 	|	 prediction: B-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999855407Z 	word 7: canada 	|	 prediction: I-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999859257Z 	word 8: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999861067Z 	word 9: made 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999862827Z 	word 10: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999864577Z 	word 11: subsidiary 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999866367Z 	word 12: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999868117Z sentence 0
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999869807Z 	word 0: pratt 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999871567Z 	word 1: founded 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999873327Z 	word 2: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999875077Z 	word 3: pratt 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999876867Z 	word 4: institute 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999878637Z 	word 5: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999880397Z 	word 6: 1887 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999882147Z 	word 7: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999883897Z 	word 8: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999885647Z 	word 9: its 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999887397Z 	word 10: campus 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999889167Z 	word 11: remains 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999890927Z 	word 12: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999893127Z 	word 13: focus 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999894897Z 	word 14: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999896668Z 	word 15: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999898428Z 	word 16: neighborhood 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999900197Z 	word 17: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999901957Z sentence 1
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999903628Z 	word 0: she 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999905378Z 	word 1: had 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999907128Z 	word 2: four 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999908898Z 	word 3: masts 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999910668Z 	word 4: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999912408Z 	word 5: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999914168Z 	word 6: rigged 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999915918Z 	word 7: as 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999917678Z 	word 8: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999919438Z 	word 9: barque 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999923318Z 	word 10: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999925118Z 	word 11: with 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999926878Z 	word 12: royal 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999928648Z 	word 13: over 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999930408Z 	word 14: double 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999932158Z 	word 15: topsail 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999933918Z 	word 16: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999935668Z 	word 17: topgallant 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999937438Z 	word 18: sail 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999939228Z 	word 19: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999940978Z sentence 2
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999942648Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999944408Z 	word 1: group 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999946158Z 	word 2: has 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999947909Z 	word 3: also 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999949669Z 	word 4: made 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999951418Z 	word 5: 25 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999953169Z 	word 6: music 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999954959Z 	word 7: video 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999956719Z 	word 8: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999958499Z 	word 9: their 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999960259Z 	word 10: songs 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999962019Z 	word 11: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999963769Z sentence 3
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999965439Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999967189Z 	word 1: latter 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999968949Z 	word 2: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999970709Z 	word 3: released 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999972459Z 	word 4: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999974219Z 	word 5: vanguard 	|	 prediction: B-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999976009Z 	word 6: records 	|	 prediction: I-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999977789Z 	word 7: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999979549Z sentence 4
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999981219Z 	word 0: ric 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999982999Z 	word 1: ocasek 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999984759Z 	word 2: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999989099Z 	word 3: lead 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999990979Z 	word 4: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999992789Z 	word 5: backing 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999994609Z 	word 6: vocals 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999996399Z 	word 7: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999998199Z 	word 8: rhythm 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:41.999999979Z 	word 9: guitar 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000001760Z 	word 10: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000003610Z 	word 11: keyboards 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000005450Z sentence 5
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000007160Z 	word 0: fuel 	|	 prediction: B-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000009000Z 	word 1: cell 	|	 prediction: I-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000010790Z 	word 2: vehicle 	|	 prediction: I-PROD
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000012960Z 	word 3: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000014740Z 	word 4: fcvs 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000016520Z 	word 5: or 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000018290Z 	word 6: fcevs 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000020080Z 	word 7: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000021850Z 	word 8: also 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000023620Z 	word 9: allow 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000025390Z 	word 10: running 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000027200Z 	word 11: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000029000Z 	word 12: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000030790Z 	word 13: some 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000032550Z 	word 14: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000034310Z 	word 15: non 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000036160Z 	word 16: fossil 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000037950Z 	word 17: fuels 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000039700Z 	word 18: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000041480Z 	word 19: i.e. 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000043230Z 	word 20: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000044980Z 	word 21: hydrogen 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000046791Z 	word 22: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000048580Z 	word 23: ethanol 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000050360Z 	word 24: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000054211Z 	word 25: methanol 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000056051Z 	word 26: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000057811Z 	word 27: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000059561Z 	word 28: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000061321Z 	word 29: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000063071Z 	word 30: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000064811Z 	word 31: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000066571Z sentence 6
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000068251Z 	word 0: chicago 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000070011Z 	word 1: 's 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000071771Z 	word 2: loyola 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000073671Z 	word 3: university 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000075481Z 	word 4: chicago 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000077251Z 	word 5: sets 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000079021Z 	word 6: an 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000080781Z 	word 7: example 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000082551Z 	word 8: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000084341Z 	word 9: public 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000086111Z 	word 10: transit 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000087881Z 	word 11: as 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000089651Z 	word 12: well 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000091421Z 	word 13: with 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000093181Z 	word 14: its 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000094941Z 	word 15: variety 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000096712Z 	word 16: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000098481Z 	word 17: transportation 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000100301Z 	word 18: options 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000102072Z 	word 19: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000103822Z sentence 7
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000105492Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000107252Z 	word 1: building 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000109012Z 	word 2: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000110782Z 	word 3: listed 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000112542Z 	word 4: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000114292Z 	word 5: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000118082Z 	word 6: national 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000119912Z 	word 7: register 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000121692Z 	word 8: of 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000123492Z 	word 9: historic 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000125262Z 	word 10: places 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000127072Z 	word 11: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000129102Z 	word 12: 2020 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000130872Z 	word 13: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000132642Z sentence 8
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000134322Z 	word 0: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000136072Z 	word 1: last 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000137852Z 	word 2: version 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000139622Z 	word 3: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000141382Z 	word 4: include 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000143152Z 	word 5: i2p 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000144942Z sentence 9
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000146613Z 	word 0: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000148362Z 	word 1: 2012 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000150122Z 	word 2: it 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000151883Z 	word 3: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000153643Z 	word 4: also 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000155403Z 	word 5: covered 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000157163Z 	word 6: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000158933Z 	word 7: therion 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000160693Z 	word 8: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000162463Z 	word 9: their 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000164233Z 	word 10: album 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000166033Z 	word 11: les 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000168953Z 	word 12: fleurs 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000170763Z 	word 13: du 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000172553Z 	word 14: mal 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000174313Z 	word 15: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000176193Z sentence 10
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000177883Z 	word 0: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000179653Z 	word 1: rotten 	|	 prediction: B-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000181483Z 	word 2: tomatoes 	|	 prediction: I-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000185353Z 	word 3: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000187173Z 	word 4: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000188933Z 	word 5: film 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000190683Z 	word 6: has 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000192443Z 	word 7: an 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000194203Z 	word 8: approval 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000195983Z 	word 9: rating 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000197754Z 	word 10: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000199503Z 	word 11: 66 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000201264Z 	word 12: % 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000203024Z 	word 13: based 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000204774Z 	word 14: on 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000206524Z 	word 15: 127 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000208304Z 	word 16: reviews 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000210094Z 	word 17: with 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000211844Z 	word 18: an 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000213604Z 	word 19: average 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000215384Z 	word 20: rating 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000217144Z 	word 21: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000218894Z 	word 22: 6.07 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000220654Z 	word 23: / 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000222414Z 	word 24: 10 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000224164Z 	word 25: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000225924Z sentence 11
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000227604Z 	word 0: after 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000229394Z 	word 1: studying 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000231164Z 	word 2: law 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000232914Z 	word 3: at 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000234684Z 	word 4: university 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000236474Z 	word 5: of 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000238254Z 	word 6: paris 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000240034Z 	word 7: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000241794Z 	word 8: paris 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000243575Z 	word 9: from 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000245344Z 	word 10: 1955 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000249315Z 	word 11: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000251155Z 	word 12: 1965 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000252925Z 	word 13: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000254675Z 	word 14: he 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000256455Z 	word 15: earned 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000258225Z 	word 16: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000259975Z 	word 17: ph 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000261725Z 	word 18: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000263485Z 	word 19: d 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000265235Z 	word 20: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000266995Z 	word 21: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000268755Z 	word 22: 1966 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000270515Z 	word 23: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000272275Z sentence 12
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000273965Z 	word 0: peter 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000275735Z 	word 1: b. 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000277525Z 	word 2: kyne 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000279315Z 	word 3: spanish 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000281095Z 	word 4: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000282875Z 	word 5: american 	|	 prediction: B-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000284695Z 	word 6: war 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000286465Z 	word 7: veteran 	|	 prediction: I-CW
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000288235Z 	word 8: ( 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000290015Z 	word 9: philippines 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000291805Z 	word 10: ) 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000293565Z 	word 11: ; 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000295325Z 	word 12: prolific 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000297105Z 	word 13: western 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000298876Z 	word 14: author 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000300646Z 	word 15: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000302406Z sentence 13
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000304086Z 	word 0: sultan 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000305856Z 	word 1: is 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000307626Z 	word 2: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000309376Z 	word 3: village 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000313346Z 	word 4: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000315146Z 	word 5: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000316906Z 	word 6: bolu 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000318686Z 	word 7: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000320456Z 	word 8: bolu 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000322226Z 	word 9: province 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000324016Z 	word 10: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000325776Z 	word 11: turkey 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000327556Z 	word 12: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000329316Z sentence 14
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000330996Z 	word 0: cafritz 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000332766Z 	word 1: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000334516Z 	word 2: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000336276Z 	word 3: first 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000338036Z 	word 4: collector 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000339806Z 	word 5: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000341556Z 	word 6: many 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000343337Z 	word 7: visual 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000345117Z 	word 8: artists 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000346877Z 	word 9: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000348626Z 	word 10: has 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000350397Z 	word 11: sponsored 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000352187Z 	word 12: many 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000353937Z 	word 13: projects 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000355717Z 	word 14: including 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000357487Z 	word 15: spike 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000359277Z 	word 16: lee 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000361057Z 	word 17: malcolm 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000363687Z 	word 18: x 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000365477Z 	word 19: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000367247Z sentence 15
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000368937Z 	word 0: hospitalfield 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000370737Z 	word 1: house 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000372517Z 	word 2: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000374267Z 	word 3: a 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000379467Z 	word 4: baronial 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000381317Z 	word 5: mansion 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000383087Z 	word 6: to 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000384837Z 	word 7: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000386597Z 	word 8: west 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000388357Z 	word 9: of 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000390127Z 	word 10: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000391877Z 	word 11: town 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000393638Z 	word 12: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000395398Z 	word 13: houses 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000397158Z 	word 14: an 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000398928Z 	word 15: educational 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000400728Z 	word 16: charity 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000402518Z 	word 17: promoting 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000404318Z 	word 18: contemporary 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000406128Z 	word 19: arts 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000407888Z 	word 20: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000409658Z sentence 16
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000411338Z 	word 0: 9 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000413088Z 	word 1: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000414868Z 	word 2: sam 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000416668Z 	word 3: allardyce 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000418448Z 	word 4: leaves 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000420228Z 	word 5: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000421988Z 	word 6: manager 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000423778Z 	word 7: 's 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000425548Z 	word 8: position 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000427318Z 	word 9: at 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000429078Z 	word 10: newcastle 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000430868Z 	word 11: united 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000432648Z 	word 12: f.c. 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000434428Z 	word 13: by 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000436178Z 	word 14: mutual 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000437978Z 	word 15: agreement 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000439758Z 	word 16: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000443379Z sentence 17
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000445099Z 	word 0: november 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000446859Z 	word 1: 2 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000448619Z 	word 2: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000450389Z 	word 3: qantas 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000452159Z 	word 4: begins 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000453939Z 	word 5: its 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000455689Z 	word 6: first 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000457439Z 	word 7: scheduled 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000459199Z 	word 8: flights 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000460959Z 	word 9: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000462709Z 	word 10: between 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000464459Z 	word 11: charleville 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000466259Z 	word 12: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000468009Z 	word 13: cloncurry 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000469779Z 	word 14: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000471529Z sentence 18
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000473199Z 	word 0: his 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000474949Z 	word 1: father 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000476709Z 	word 2: was 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.000478479Z 	word 3: an 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786238560Z 	word 4: international 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786267971Z 	word 5: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786270281Z 	word 6: both 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786272181Z 	word 7: rugby 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786274051Z 	word 8: union 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786275911Z 	word 9: and 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786277841Z 	word 10: rugby 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786279661Z 	word 11: league 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786281481Z 	word 12: , 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786283261Z 	word 13: having 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786285341Z 	word 14: played 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786287101Z 	word 15: for 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786288961Z 	word 16: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786304481Z 	word 17: great 	|	 prediction: B-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786306441Z 	word 18: britain 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786308272Z 	word 19: national 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786310512Z 	word 20: rugby 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786312322Z 	word 21: league 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786314142Z 	word 22: team 	|	 prediction: I-GRP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786315952Z 	word 23: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786317762Z sentence 19
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786319502Z 	word 0: adebayo 	|	 prediction: B-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786321292Z 	word 1: o. 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786323082Z 	word 2: ogunlesi 	|	 prediction: I-PER
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786324912Z 	word 3: – 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786327212Z 	word 4: chairman 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786329082Z 	word 5: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786330902Z 	word 6: managing 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786332712Z 	word 7: partner 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786334522Z 	word 8: at 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786336332Z 	word 9: global 	|	 prediction: B-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786338182Z 	word 10: infrastructure 	|	 prediction: I-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786340062Z 	word 11: partners 	|	 prediction: I-CORP
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786341902Z sentence 20
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786343632Z 	word 0: krauthamer 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786345442Z 	word 1: has 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786347222Z 	word 2: resided 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786349032Z 	word 3: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786350822Z 	word 4: washington, 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786352662Z 	word 5: d.c. 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786354493Z 	word 6: and 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786356273Z 	word 7: silver 	|	 prediction: B-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786358083Z 	word 8: spring 	|	 prediction: I-LOC
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786359893Z 	word 9: since 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786361723Z 	word 10: 1970 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786363523Z 	word 11: . 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786365303Z sentence 21
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786367003Z 	word 0: in 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786370533Z 	word 1: 1950 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786372383Z 	word 2: the 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786374143Z 	word 3: main 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786375933Z 	word 4: shareholder 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786377723Z 	word 5: handelsbanken 	|	 prediction: O
2022-04-19T19:05:42.786379543Z 	word 6: sold 	|	 prediction: O
